(Sheldon:)I always thought
I was more like a cuckoo bird.
(Sheldon:)A superior creature whose egg is placed
in the nest of ordinary birds.
(Sheldon:)The newly hatched cuckoo
eats all the food...
(Sheldon:)...leaving the ordinary siblings
to starve to death.
(Sheldon:)Luckily for you,
that's where the metaphor ended.
(Missy:)I thought it ended at cuckoo.
(Missy:)Now, you listen to me.
If you wanna start acting like a brother
who cares about me, terrific.
(Missy:)Bring it on.
(Missy:)But you try one time to tell me
who I should be sleeping with...
...and you and I are gonna go round the way
we did when we were little. Remember?
- I have an alternate proposal.
- Go on.
(Sheldon:)You donate eggs.
We will place them in cryogenic storage.
(Sheldon:)I will find an appropriate sperm donor
for your eggs...
(Sheldon:)...have them fertilized
and implanted in you.
(Sheldon:)That way, everybody wins.